<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
   <template id="csa_general_agreement">
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
            
    <!-- ................. CSA FOR THE BORROWING CLUB Below NWLC Agreement ...................... -->
            
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
       <t t-call="web.html_container">
           <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
                <t t-if="o.company_id.id == 1">
                    <!-- <style>
                        @media print {
                            .oe_structure .header{
                                display: none !important;
                            } 
                        

                            .oe_structure {
                                page-break-after: always;
                            }
                        }
                    </style> -->
                    
                    <div class="page">
                        <t t-call="web.basic_layout">
                        <div class="oe_structure">
                            <img t-att-src="'/nwlc_crm_ext/static/src/img/nwlc_cover_csa.png'"/>
                        </div>
                            <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                        
            <div class="header text-center mt-3">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-4">
                        <img t-if="o.company_id.logo and o.company_id.id == 1" t-att-src="image_data_uri(o.company_id.logo)" style="height: 80px; margin-top: 15px;" alt="header"/>
                    </div>
                    
                    <div class="col-8" style="margin-top:60px;font-family:Montserrat">
                        <h3>CUSTOMER SERVICE AGREEMENT</h3>
                    </div>
                </div>
                        
                    
            </div>
            
            <div class="mt-3">
                <!-- <div class="row">
                    <center>
                        <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo and doc.company_id.id == 1" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="height: 120px;width:300px;" alt="header"/>
                        <br/>
                    </center>
                </div>
                <h4 style="text-align:center;margin-top:18px;font-family:Times New Roman;font-style:italic">You're one step closer to <b>financial freedom</b></h4>
                <div style="page-break-before: always;"/> -->
                <p>
                    Nationwide Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC, a Florida limited liability company
                    (sometimes referred to in this Agreement as "Nationwide") and Customer (sometimes referred
                    to in this Agreement as "Borrower," "I", "me," "my," "you," and "your") have agreed that
                    Nationwide shall provide certain services in relation to you possibly obtaining a loan.
                    Nationwide and Customer agree as follows:
                </p>

                <h5><b>GENERAL SERVICES OVERVIEW</b></h5>
                <ol>
                    <li>Nationwide represents that it is not acting as a lender or acting on behalf of any lender 
                    with respect to this Agreement. Thus, Nationwide is not affiliated with any of the lenders to 
                    which it will submit loan applications on your behalf. Nationwide utilizes its considerable 
                    resources and data pool, along with its experienced professional staff in an effort to find 
                    you the most suitable loan package(s) to fit your borrowing criteria.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>Services provided by Nationwide ("Nationwide Services") consist of researching potential 
                    loans/lenders applicable to your needs, advising you on such available loan products, referring 
                    you to the lenders providing applicable loan products, and consulting with you throughout that 
                    process. Therefore, Nationwide will submit or refer you to multiple lenders in our database. 
                    Each individual lender will do its own credit check and underwriting.  As such, Nationwide has
                    no liability for the actions/decisions of any such referred lenders or whether the final loan 
                    product offered by any lender that meets the Borrower’s expectations as to terms, interest rates 
                    or lender fees. You acknowledge and agree that the responsibilities of Nationwide shall be limited
                    to the services listed above, and as such Nationwide shall not engage in any negotiations whatsoever
                    on your behalf and Nationwide shall have no continuing obligations, duties, responsibilities, role,
                    part in the negotiations, or in the relationship between the lender and you, whatsoever.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I fully understand and acknowledge that the loan packages offered by the lenders located by 
                    Nationwide are also available to me without utilizing the services of Nationwide, and therefore,
                    I could have tried to locate such packages on my own without the need to incur the Consulting Fee
                    identified in the agreement. However, I have elected to utilize the services of Nationwide and pay
                    the Consulting Fee as specified herein. I have elected to retain the services of Nationwide because
                    Nationwide has experience in the consumer loan industry and has vast resources and knowledge to 
                    assist me to properly complete the application process, which will increase my chances of finding
                    a suitable loan package(s) with the best rates and terms available for my needs</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>THE PROCESS</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I understand that by proceeding, I am authorizing Nationwide to represent me and act on my behalf 
                    for the loan application process, in written form, electronically, verbally, or any other means in 
                    which it is required in order to obtain the best loan option available for me. I further authorize
                    Nationwide to communicate with all lenders on my behalf, verbally or through the e-mail process.
                    I understand that Nationwide will need to create an email on my behalf in order to communicate 
                    with various lenders and organize applications submitted on my behalf, therefore ,  I grant Nationwide
                    the authority to  create and access an email on my behalf. </li><br/>
                    <!-- <div style="page-break-before: always;"/> -->
                    <li>I also grant Nationwide the authority to access my credit report and I understand that 
                    Nationwide may pull and view my credit report for up to 120 days after I execute this Agreement.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>If any actions of the Borrower are necessary or appropriate in connection with the loan applications
                    contemplated hereunder, then the Borrower shall use his/her best efforts to perform such actions in a 
                    timely manner and to cooperate with and assist Nationwide’s efforts, including but not limited to, 
                    speaking (dealing) directly with a lender,  returning telephone calls, responding to communications
                    including e-mails, verifying your identity, and  furnishing all documents and information requested by
                    Nationwide and/or a lender.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>Nationwide agrees that you are never under any obligation to accept or receive a loan or a line of credit.
                    Nationwide cannot and will not accept any loans on your behalf without your approval. Nationwide endeavors to 
                    provide you with the best options to choose from but all decisions regarding any loan offers, including closing
                    on any of the loan options is solely your choice to make.</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>CONSULTING FEE AND ACH PAYMENT</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>Nationwide does not charge an UPFRONT FEE. Nationwide works completely risk free for you. The only time
                    a charge for services is due to Nationwide, is after you are approved by a lender and receive access to the
                    funds, or under the circumstances set forth in paragraph (10)  below. Any fees due and payable by you to Nationwide
                    are for Nationwide Services I understand that some lenders have fees and that these fees are separate and in addition
                    to any fees you owe Nationwide.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I agree to pay Nationwide a one-time Consulting Fee of ( <u><span t-field="o.change_fee"/></u> %) of the total dollar amount I accept and 
                    receive from a bank or lending institution as a result of the services provided by Nationwide. I understand
                    that this Consulting Fee is payable to Nationwide by me within 48 hours from the time I receive access to 
                    funding. I understand that I will be charged and will owe Nationwide a late fee of five (5%) percent of the
                    Consulting Fee if Nationwide does not receive the Consulting Fee within 72 hours of the date, I receive access
                    to funding. I understand that in such event I will also be responsible for attorney’s fees and costs incurred 
                    by Nationwide in connection with efforts to collect the Consulting Fee.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I agree not to circumvent Nationwide by applying for and/or obtaining financing from any of the lenders 
                    located by Nationwide for a period of 90 days from the date of execution of this Agreement, without notifying
                    Nationwide and paying the consulting fee hereunder. I understand that if I do, I will be in breach of this Agreement
                    and I will be liable to pay the Consulting Fee specified in paragraph (9) below, based on the total dollar amount of
                    any such funding. I understand that in such event I will also be responsible for attorney’s fees and costs incurred by
                    Nationwide in connection with efforts to collect the Consulting Fee.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I agree that the Consulting Fee due under this Agreement shall be made through an automated clearing house (“ACH”)
                    transfer from my designated account directly to Nationwide. Accordingly, upon execution of this Agreement, I agree to 
                    deliver to Nationwide a completed One Time <b><u>ACH Authorization Form</u></b>, (a copy of which is attached and incorporated herein)
                    whereby  I hereby irrevocably authorize Nationwide to initiate an ACH  transfer from my account to Nationwide in the amount 
                    of the fee due under this Agreement. For so long as my obligations under this Agreement remain outstanding, I agree to: (i)
                    not revoke Nationwide authority to initiate ACH debit as hereby contemplated; (ii) not change, modify, close or otherwise 
                    affect the account; (iii) direct any lender deposit all loans contemplated herein into the account designated in the ACH 
                    Form; and (iv) be responsible for all costs, expenses, or other fees and charges incurred by Nationwide as a result of any
                    failed or returned ACH debits, whether resulting from insufficient sums being available in the account, or otherwise.
                    I hereby certify that I am the authorized user of this bank account designated in the ACH Form and I will not dispute
                    the transactions contemplated hereunder with my bank, so long as the transactions correspond to the terms indicated in
                    this Agreement.</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>DISPUTE RESOLUTION</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I understand and acknowledge that as part of its service promise, Nationwide has a mandatory dispute resolution process. 
                    If I am dissatisfied with the services provided by Nationwide, I must first contact my customer service representative via 
                    e-mail or telephone and request a Dispute Resolution Form. I must then complete and submit that form via e-mail as instructed 
                    on the form. Nationwide will respond to all dispute resolution requests within two business days (weekends and legal holidays
                    are not included) of receipt of a properly submitted Dispute Resolution Form.</li>
                <!--</ol>-->
                <br/>
                <h5>LOANS EXCLUDED FROM CONSULTING FEE</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I understand that I will not have to pay the Consulting Fee provided for in this Agreement for loans I obtain from lenders with
                    which I have applied for an unsecured loan, credit card, or line of credit within the past (60) sixty days, as listed in paragraph
                    (14) below. I further understand that I will not have to pay the Consulting Fee provided for in this Agreement for loans I obtain 
                    from lenders with which I currently have an open unsecured loan or line of credit, as listed in paragraph (15) below. Nationwide 
                    will not apply for loans on my behalf with the lenders I list in paragraphs (14) and (15) below.</li><br/>
                
                    <li>In the past 60 days have you or anyone representing you applied for an unsecured loan, credit card or line of credit? If so, 
                    below please list the names of those institutions to which you have applied.<br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                    </li><br/>
                    <li>
                        Please list below all open unsecured loans or lines of credit:<br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                    </li>
                <!--</ol>-->
                <br/>
                
                <h5>Communication Consent</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>By signing this document, you authorize Nationwide to communicate with you by using the telephone number provided by you
                    and any other telephone numbers associated or related to you that may be provided to us by you in the future. You consent to
                    allow Nationwide to contact you by phone, text, email, mail, or by artificial or pre-recorded voice, even if you have listed
                    yourself on any <b>Do-Not-Call List</b>. You also agree that any person or entity contacting you pursuant to your consent here may 
                    use automatic telephone dialing system, even if the telephone number you provided (or any telephone number associated with 
                    you) is connected to a mobile phone and even if you might be charged for the call. Your consent to receive automated calls
                    or text messages is not required for any purchase or availability of goods/services from Nationwide; if you do not consent, 
                    you may call us at 1-888-463-5255 to continue your inquiry.</li>
                <!--</ol>-->
                <br/>
                
                <h5>WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I represent and warrant that (a) I have the full right and authority to enter into this agreement, make the consents and 
                    authorizations herein, and to grant the rights herein granted and agreed to be granted; (b) I have not made and shall not make
                    any grant or agreement which will or might impair, encumber or conflict with any of the rights granted to Nationwide;(c) I shall
                    at all times comply with any and all laws, statutes, regulations, codes and ordinances applicable to any financing; and (d) all 
                    information and representations provided by me shall be true and accurate</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I understand and agree that if any lender inquires as to whether I am working with a third party in relation to obtaining a 
                    loan, I must disclose to the lender that I am working with Nationwide. In the event of such lender inquiry, I understand and 
                    agree that I must notify Nationwide and provide the name of the lender(s) and the name of the lender’s representative to which 
                    disclosure was made</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I understand and agree that Nationwide will require me to review and approve any and all information provided to my loan 
                    advisor prior to submission of any applications. I also agree that I will promptly notify Nationwide if any of the information
                    provided later becomes inaccurate or changed for any reason. Further, I will promptly notify Nationwide if I provide any information
                    to any prospective lender that differs from the information I provided to Nationwide or if I alter any information submitted to 
                    any lender.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I shall defend, indemnify and hold harmless Nationwide (and/or its shareholders, directors, members, managers, officers, 
                    representatives, employees, successors, licensees and assigns) from and against any and all claims, demands, losses, damages,
                    actions, liabilities, judgments, penalties, costs and expenses (including, without limitation, attorneys 'fees and court costs,
                    whether or not in connection with litigation) arising out of or otherwise relating to your breach of any representation or warranty
                    hereunder and/or related to any claims arising from any negotiations or agreements with any lender</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->
                
                    <h5>CANCELLATION POLICIES</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>This  Agreement can only be canceled after Nationwide receives written cancellation provided by me. Any such cancellation shall
                    not relieve me from any payment or other obligations and responsibilities under paragraphs (9) and (10) above. From the date of 
                    written cancellation, Nationwide has the right to review and access any and all credit reports for verification purposes only.
                    I agree and accept that I do not have the right to cancel this ninety-day (90-day) credit review process.</li><br/>
                
                    <h5>COMMERCIAL LOANS</h5>
                    
                    <li>Nationwide Services are also available for commercial loans. In the event that you desire Nationwide Services regarding a commercial loan,
                    including but not limited to merchant cash advance or accounts receivables based loans, then all terms and conditions of this Agreement shall 
                    apply to any commercial loan, including but not limited to consents, authorizations, consulting fees, warranties and representations. 
                    In addition to any information required as specified above, you understand that in order to provide Nationwide Services in relation to a
                    commercial loan it may be necessary for Nationwide to obtain consumer, personal, business and investigative reports and other information
                    about you and/or your company (if the loan is to be made to an entity), including credit card processor statements and bank statements, from
                    one or more consumer reporting agencies, such as TransUnion, Experian and Equifax, and from other credit bureaus, banks, creditors and other
                    third parties. It may also be necessary to transmit the foregoing information to third parties in order to provide of Nationwide Services in
                    connection with a commercial loan. You  also consent to the release by any creditor or financial institution of any of the foregoing information
                    to Nationwide and/or its representatives , successors, assigns and designees.  You authorize Nationwide to obtain and/or transmit the foregoing 
                    information. You also warrant that you are authorized to act on behalf of and bind any entity for which you request that Nationwide Services be
                    provided. You agree that you are individually responsible for payment of consulting fees regardless of whether the loan is funded to an entity.</li><br/>
                
                    <h5>MISCELLANEOUS</h5>
                    
                    <li>This Agreement contains the entire agreement of the Parties, and it may only be modified by an agreement in writing signed by
                    all Parties. This Agreement shall be construed and interpreted in accordance with the substantive laws of the State of Florida, 
                    without regard to its conflict of laws principles. This Agreement is deemed entered into in the State of Florida and for any 
                    dispute arising out of or under this Agreement, or which are related to this Agreement, venue and jurisdiction shall be exclusively
                    in Broward County, Florida and the Parties hereby consent to venue and jurisdiction in Broward County, Florida. In connection with 
                    any litigation arising out of or under this Agreement, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover all costs and reasonable 
                    attorney's fees including appellate and post judgment proceedings. I hereby authorize Nationwide to communicate with me via the 
                    e-mail address I have provided.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    I agree to the aforementioned terms and conditions making this a binding contract. I understand that this Agreement is bound by 
                    electronic signature.  This electronic signature must be that of the actual individual applying for a loan otherwise it constitutes
                    forgery under any and all applicable state and federal laws, statutes, rules, and regulations. The individual "signing" this document
                    affirms that the facts stated herein are true.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    I understand that I am giving consent to Nationwide Loan Consultants and Advisors (Nationwide) permission to obtain a soft credit 
                    check to qualify me for obtaining a loan.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    I understand that by clicking on the <b>I AGREE button</b> or typing my name whichever is applicable immediately following this notice 
                    I am providing “written instructions” to Nationwide under the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA) authorizing Nationwide to obtain
                    information from my personal credit profile or other information from any credit bureau, including but not limited to, Experian,
                    TransUnion and/or Equifax. I authorize Nationwide to obtain such information solely to prequalify me for credit options.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    </li>
                
                </ol>
                
                <div class="row"><div class="col-12">
                    <span>IDENTITY VERIFICATION QUESTIONS:</span>
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-4">
                                        First Name :
                                    </div>
                                <div class="col-8">
                                    <span t-field="o.first_name"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-3">
                                        Last Name :
                                    </div>
                                <div class="col-9">
                                    <span t-field="o.last_name"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-2">Home Address :</div>
                        <div class="col-10">
                            <span t-field="o.street"/>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-4">Yearly Income :</div>
                                <div class="col-8">
                                    <span t-field="o.primary_gross_annual_income"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">Is The Income Verifiable? Yes_No :</div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span t-esc="o.is_income_verifiable"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <span>AGREE TO ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS:</span>
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-5">Signature :</div>
                                <div class="col-7"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-5">Date :</div>
                                <div class="col-7"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-6">AGREE TO ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS:</div>
                        <div class="col-6"/>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-5">Signature :</div>
                                <div class="col-7"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-7">Date :</div>
                                <div class="col-5"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                </div></div>
                <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                
                <div class="row text-left">
                    <h3><center>THIRD-PARTY AUTHORIZATION FORM</center></h3>
                </div>    
                    <p>
                        I,					with an address of						 (“Borrower” or “I” or “me” or “my”) hereby authorize 
                        <b>NATIONWIDE LOAN CONSULTANTS &amp; ADVISORS, LLC,</b> its associates, agents and/or assigns (individually and collectively
                        the “Agent”) the right to communicate with independent lenders (“Third-Parties”) on my behalf, and act as my agent,
                        under the following terms:
                        <br/>
                        <ol>
                            <li> I hereby give and grant unto my said Agent full <b>consent and authority</b> to act for me in any lawful way with 
                            respect to the consent to obtain, share, release, discuss, and otherwise provide to Third Parties, and with each
                            other, public and non-public personal information contained in or related to obtaining a consumer loan for the 
                            Borrower. This information may include but is not limited to the name, mailing address, telephone number, social
                            security number, credit score, credit report, income, account balances, program eligibility, and payment activity
                            of the Borrower.</li>
                            
                            <br/>
                            
                            <li>I understand that I will be fully responsible for reviewing any information
                            that is sent by Third Parties to my Agent.</li>
                        
                            <br/>
                            
                            <li>This Authorization expires one year from the date signed unless Borrower specifically notified 
                            Agent in writing that this Authorization is of no further force and effect.</li>
                        
                            <br/>
                            
                            <li>I understand that this Form may not be accepted by some Third Parties, 
                            and my Agent will notify me in writing if it is not accepted.</li>
                            
                            <br/>
                        
                            <li>I understand and agree that my Agent has no responsibility or liability to verify what the 
                            Third Parties do with the information provided to it by my Agent, as authorized by this Form.</li>
                        
                            <br/>
                        
                            <li>I hereby agree to indemnify and forever hold my Agent harmless from any and all actions and causes of actions, 
                            suits, claims, attorney’s fees, or demands against my Agent, resulting from my Agent discussing, or declining to 
                            discuss, my information with Third-Parties, or resulting from my Agent providing, or declining to provide, any documents
                            or other information to Third-Parties.</li>
                        </ol>
                        <br/>
                        <span> I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS THIRD-PARTY AUTHORIZATION.</span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>Borrower's Signature: </span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>Borrower Printed Name: </span>
                        <span t-field="o.full_name"/>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>Date:</span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                    </p>



                                            <!--For Maryland-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'MD' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h4><center><u>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</u></center></h4>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, at any time prior to midnight of 
                    the third business day after the date the contract is signed. If you cancel, any payment made by you 
                    under this contract will be returned within 10 days following receipt by the seller of your cancellation
                    notice. To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed and dated copy of this cancellation notice, or
                    any other written notice, to </p><br/>
                    
                    <p>Nationwide Loan Consultants and Advisors, LLC 555 SW 12th Ave. Pompano Beach, FL 33069
                        Not later than midnight 	(Date)______________I hereby cancel this transaction.</p><br/>
                        
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-5">(Date) :</div>
                                    <div class="col-7"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">(Customer Signature) :</div>
                                    <div class="col-5"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    
                    </t>
                    
                                            <!--For Oklohama-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'OK' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days from the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract, will be returned with ten (10) days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice. To cancel this contract, mail or 
                    deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, or any other written notice to Nationwide
                    Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069 not later than
                    midnight on___________</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction,______________________(date).</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Signature :</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h4><center><u><b>INFORMATION STATEMENT</b></u></center></h4>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>Nationwide Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC </p>
                    
                    <p>555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202</p>
                    
                    <p>Pompano Beach, FL 33069</p>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>We are required by law to provide this information statement before the execution of a contract or 
                    before the receipt of any money or other valuable consideration.</p>
                    
                    <ol>
                        <li>You have the right to review any file maintained by any consumer credit reporting agency, as provided under 
                        the Federal Fair Credit Reporting Act, 15 U.S.C., Sections 1681 through 1681t.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>You have the right to review the above-mentioned file at no charge if a request is made to the 
                        consumer credit reporting agency within thirty (30) days after receiving notice that credit has been 
                        denied. If credit was not denied the approximate price to review such file will be $100.00.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>You have the right to dispute the completeness or accuracy of any item contained in your file 
                        which is maintained by a consumer credit reporting agency.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>In this paragraph give your customer a detailed description of the services to be performed 
                        by your company including the total amount the buyer will have to pay, or become obligated to pay,
                        for your services.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>You have the right to proceed against the bond or trust account we are required by law to maintain.
                        The name and address of the surety company that issued the bond is International Fidelity Insurance 
                        Company.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                    </ol>
                    
                    <p>I have received a copy of the above information statement.</p>
                    
                    
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>_______________________________</p>
                    
                    <p>Customer Signature</p>
                    
                    <p>_______________________________</p>
                    
                    <p>Date</p>
                    
                    
                    </t>
                    
                    
                                            <!--For Nebraska-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'NE' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days from the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract, will be returned with ten (10) days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice. To cancel this contract, mail or 
                    deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, or any other written notice to Nationwide
                    Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069 not later than
                    midnight on___________</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction,______________________(date).</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Signature :</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    </t>
                                                
                                                
                                                
                                            <!--For Pennsylvania-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'PA' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days from the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract, will be returned with ten (10) days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice.</p>
                    
                    <p> To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, 
                    or any other written notice to:</p>
                    
                    <p><b>Nationwide Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069</b> not later than
                    midnight on___________</p>
                    
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction,______________________(date).</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        
                        <table class="table-bordered">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:350px;padding:10px">Data</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:350px;padding:10px">Purchaser's Signature</td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                    </t>
                    
                    
                    
                                            <!--For Wisconsin-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'WI' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days after the date on <b>which the contract is signed.</b> </p>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract will be returned with 15 days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice.</p>
                    
                    <p> To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed and dated copy of this cancellation notice, 
                    or any other written notice to: Nationwide Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC at 555 SW 12th 
                    Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069 not later than midnight (Date)___________</p>
                    
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction,______________________(date).</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-8">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-6">Print Consumer Name</div>
                                    <div class="col-6">_________________________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <br/>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-6">Signature :</div>
                                    <div class="col-6">_________________________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <br/>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-6">Date :</div>
                                    <div class="col-6">_________________________________</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-4">
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        
                    </t>
                    
                                            <!--For West Virginia-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'WV' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within three (3) days from the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract, will be returned with ten (10) days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice.</p>
                    
                    <p> To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, 
                    or any other written notice to:</p>
                    
                    <p><b>Nationwide Loan Consultants &amp; Advisors, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069</b> not later than
                    midnight on___________</p>
                    
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction,______________________(date).</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        
                        <table class="table-bordered">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:350px;padding:10px">Data</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:350px;padding:10px">Purchaser's Signature</td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                    </t>
                    
                    


            </div>
                    </t>
                    </div>
                </t>


            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
            
               <!-- ................. CSA FOR THE BORROWING CLUB ...................... -->
            
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
            <!-- xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->



                <t t-if="o.company_id.id == 3">
                    <t t-call="web.basic_layout">
                        <div class="page">
                        <div class="oe_structure">
                            <img t-att-src="'/nwlc_crm_ext/static/src/img/tbc_cover_csa.png'" />
                        </div>
                            <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    
            <div class="header text-center mt-5">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-4">
                        <img t-if="o.company_id.logo and o.company_id.id == 3" t-att-src="image_data_uri(o.company_id.logo)" style="height: 80px;margin-top:30px;" alt="header"/>
                    </div>
                    
                    <div class="col-8" style="margin-top:60px;font-family:Montserrat">
                        <h3>CUSTOMER SERVICE AGREEMENT</h3>
                        <!-- <h3><t t-esc="o.company_id.id"/></h3> -->
                    </div>
                </div>
                        
                    
            </div>
            <div class="mt-3">
                <!-- <div class="row">
                    <center>
                        <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo and doc.company_id.id == 1" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="height: 120px;width:300px;" alt="header"/>
                        <br/>
                    </center>
                </div>
                <h4 style="text-align:center;margin-top:18px;font-family:Times New Roman;font-style:italic">You're one step closer to <b>financial freedom</b></h4>
                <div style="page-break-before: always;"/> -->
                <p>
                    The Borrowing Club, LLC, a Florida limited liability company (sometimes referred to in 
                    this Agreement as “TBC”) and Customer (sometimes referred to in this Agreement as 
                    “Borrower,” “I”, “me,” “my,” “you,” and “your”) have agreed that TBC shall provide 
                    certain services in relation to you possibly obtaining a loan. TBC and Customer 
                    agree as follows: 
                </p>

                <h5><b>GENERAL SERVICES OVERVIEW</b></h5>
                <ol>
                    <li>TBC represents that it is not acting as a lender or acting on behalf of any lender with 
                    respect to this Agreement. Thus, TBC is not affiliated with any of the lenders to which 
                    it will submit loan applications on your behalf. TBC utilizes its considerable resources 
                    and data pool, along with its experienced professional staff in an effort to find you the 
                    most suitable loan package(s) to fit your borrowing criteria.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>Services provided by TBC (“TBC Services”) consist of researching potential loans/lenders 
                    applicable to your needs, advising you on such available loan products, referring you to the 
                    lenders providing applicable loan products, and consulting with you throughout that process. 
                    Therefore, TBC will submit or refer you to multiple lenders in our database. Each individual 
                    lender will do its own credit check and underwriting.  As such, TBC has no liability for the 
                    actions/decisions of any such referred lenders or whether the final loan product offered by 
                    any lender that meets the Borrower’s expectations as to terms, interest rates or lender fees. 
                    You acknowledge and agree that the responsibilities of TBC shall be limited to the services 
                    listed above, and as such TBC shall not engage in any negotiations whatsoever on your behalf 
                    and TBC shall have no continuing obligations, duties, responsibilities, role, part in the 
                    negotiations, or in the relationship between the lender and you, whatsoever.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li><u>I fully understand and acknowledge that the loan packages offered by the lenders located 
                    by TBC are also available to me without utilizing the services of TBC, and therefore, I could 
                    have tried to locate such packages on my own without the need to incur the Consulting Fee identified 
                    in the agreement. However, I have elected to utilize the services of TBC and pay the Consulting Fee 
                    as specified herein. I have elected to retain the services of TBC because TBC has experience in the 
                    consumer loan industry and has vast resources and knowledge to assist me to properly complete the 
                    application process, which will increase my chances of finding a suitable loan package(s) with the 
                    best rates and terms available for my needs.</u></li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>THE PROCESS</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I understand that by proceeding, I am authorizing TBC to represent me and act on my behalf for 
                    the loan application process, in written form, electronically, verbally, or any other means in which 
                    it is required in order to obtain the best loan option available for me. I further authorize TBC to 
                    communicate with all lenders on my behalf, verbally or through the e-mail process. I understand that 
                    TBC will need to create an email on my behalf in order to communicate with various lenders and organize 
                    applications submitted on my behalf, therefore ,  I grant TBC the authority to  create and access an 
                    email on my behalf.  </li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I also grant TBC the authority to access my credit report and I understand that TBC may pull and 
                    view my credit report for up to 120 days after I execute this Agreement. </li>

                    <li>If any actions of the Borrower are necessary or appropriate in connection with the loan applications 
                    contemplated hereunder, then the Borrower shall use his/her best efforts to perform such actions in a 
                    timely manner and to cooperate with and assist TBC’s efforts, including but not limited to, speaking 
                    (dealing) directly with a lender,  returning telephone calls, responding to communications including 
                    e-mails, verifying your identity, and  furnishing all documents and information requested by TBC and/or 
                    a lender.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li> TBC agrees that you are never under any obligation to accept or receive a loan or a line of credit. 
                    TBC cannot and will not accept any loans on your behalf without your approval. TBC endeavors to provide 
                    you with the best options to choose from but all decisions regarding any loan offers, including closing 
                    on any of the loan options is solely your choice to make.</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>CONSULTING FEE AND ACH PAYMENT</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>TBC does not charge an UPFRONT FEE. TBC works completely risk free for you. The only time a charge 
                    for services is due to TBC, is after you are approved by a lender and receive access to the funds, or 
                    under the circumstances set forth in paragraph (10)  below. Any fees due and payable by you to TBC are 
                    for TBC Services I understand that some lenders have fees and that these fees are separate and in 
                    addition to any fees you owe TBC.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li> I agree to pay TBC a one-time Consulting Fee of (_____%) of the total dollar amount I accept 
                    and receive from a bank or lending institution as a result of the services provided by TBC. I understand 
                    that this Consulting Fee is payable to TBC by me within 48 hours from the time I receive access to funding. 
                    I understand that I will be charged and will owe TBC a late fee of five (5%) percent of the Consulting Fee 
                    if TBC does not receive the Consulting Fee within 72 hours of the date, I receive access to funding. I 
                    understand that in such event I will also be responsible for attorney’s fees and costs incurred by TBC 
                    in connection with efforts to collect the Consulting Fee.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I agree not to circumvent TBC by applying for and/or obtaining financing from any of the lenders 
                    located by TBC for a period of 90 days from the date of execution of this Agreement, without notifying 
                    TBC and paying the consulting fee hereunder. I understand that if I do, I will be in breach of this 
                    Agreement and I will be liable to pay the Consulting Fee specified in paragraph (9) below, based on 
                    the total dollar amount of any such funding. I understand that in such event I will also be responsible 
                    for attorney’s fees and costs incurred by TBC in connection with efforts to collect the Consulting Fee.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I agree that the Consulting Fee due under this Agreement shall be made through an automated clearing house 
                    (“ACH”) transfer from my designated account directly to TBC. Accordingly, upon execution of this Agreement, I 
                    agree to deliver to TBC a completed One Time <b>ACH Authorization Form</b>, (a copy of which is attached and incorporated 
                    herein) whereby  I hereby irrevocably authorize TBC to initiate an ACH  transfer from my account to TBC in the 
                    amount of the fee due under this Agreement. For so long as my obligations under this Agreement remain outstanding, 
                    I agree to: (i) not revoke TBC authority to initiate ACH debit as hereby contemplated; (ii) not change, modify, 
                    close or otherwise affect the account; (iii) direct any lender deposit all loans contemplated herein into the 
                    account designated in the ACH Form; and (iv) be responsible for all costs, expenses, or other fees and charges 
                    incurred by TBC as a result of any failed or returned ACH debits, whether resulting from insufficient sums being 
                    available in the account, or otherwise. I hereby certify that I am the authorized user of this bank account 
                    designated in the ACH Form and I will not dispute the transactions contemplated hereunder with my bank, so 
                    long as the transactions correspond to the terms indicated in this Agreement.</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>DISPUTE RESOLUTION</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I understand and acknowledge that as part of its service promise, TBC has a mandatory dispute resolution process. 
                    If I am dissatisfied with the services provided by TBC, I must first contact my customer service representative via 
                    e-mail or telephone and request a Dispute Resolution Form. I must then complete and submit that form via e-mail as 
                    instructed on the form. TBC will respond to all dispute resolution requests within two business days (weekends and 
                    legal holidays are not included) of receipt of a properly submitted Dispute Resolution Form.</li>
                <!--</ol>-->

                <h5>LOANS EXCLUDED FROM CONSULTING FEE</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I understand that I will not have to pay the Consulting Fee provided for in this Agreement for loans I 
                    obtain from lenders with which I have applied for an unsecured loan, credit card, or line of credit within 
                    the past (60) sixty days, as listed in paragraph (14) below. I further understand that I will not have to 
                    pay the Consulting Fee provided for in this Agreement for loans I obtain from lenders with which I currently 
                    have an open unsecured loan or line of credit, as listed in paragraph (15) below. TBC will not apply for loans 
                    on my behalf with the lenders I list in paragraphs (14) and (15) below.</li><br/>
                
                    <li> In the past 60 days have you or anyone representing you applied for an unsecured loan, credit card or line 
                    of credit? If so, below please list the names of those institutions to which you have applied.<br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                    </li><br/>
                    <li>
                        Please list below all open unsecured loans or lines of credit:<br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-4">Bank Name:</div>
                            <div class="col-8"/>
                        </div>
                    </li>
                <!--</ol>-->
                <br/>
                
                <h5>Communication Consent</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li> By signing this document, you authorize TBC to communicate with you by using the telephone number provided by 
                    you and any other telephone numbers associated or related to you that may be provided to us by you in the future. 
                    You consent to allow TBC to contact you by phone, text, email, mail, or by artificial or pre-recorded voice, even 
                    if you have listed yourself on any <b>Do-Not-Call</b> List. You also agree that any person or entity contacting you pursuant 
                    to your consent here may use automatic telephone dialing system, even if the telephone number you provided (or any 
                    telephone number associated with you) is connected to a mobile phone and even if you might be charged for the call. 
                    Your consent to receive automated calls or text messages is not required for any purchase or availability of goods/services 
                    from TBC; if you do not consent, you may call us at 1-888-463-5255 to continue your inquiry.</li>
                <!--</ol>-->
                <br/>
                
                <h5>WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>I represent and warrant that (a) I have the full right and authority to enter into this agreement, make the consents and 
                    authorizations herein, and to grant the rights herein granted and agreed to be granted; (b) I have not made and shall not make 
                    any grant or agreement which will or might impair, encumber or conflict with any of the rights granted to TBC;(c) I shall at all 
                    times comply with any and all laws, statutes, regulations, codes and ordinances applicable to any financing; and (d) all information 
                    and representations provided by me shall be true and accurate. </li><br/>
                    
                    <li> I understand and agree that if any lender inquires as to whether I am working with a third party in relation to obtaining a loan, 
                    I must disclose to the lender that I am working with TBC. In the event of such lender inquiry, I understand and agree that I must notify 
                    TBC and provide the name of the lender(s) and the name of the lender’s representative to which disclosure was made.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li> I understand and agree that TBC will require me to review and approve any and all information provided to my loan advisor prior to 
                    submission of any applications. I also agree that I will promptly notify TBC if any of the information provided later becomes 
                    inaccurate or changed for any reason. Further, I will promptly notify TBC if I provide any information to any prospective 
                    lender that differs from the information I provided to TBC or if I alter any information submitted to any lender.</li><br/>
                    
                    <li>I shall defend, indemnify and hold harmless TBC (and/or its shareholders, directors, members, managers, officers, representatives, 
                    employees, successors, licensees and assigns) from and against any and all claims, demands, losses, damages, actions, liabilities, 
                    judgments, penalties, costs and expenses (including, without limitation, attorneys 'fees and court costs, whether or not in connection 
                    with litigation) arising out of or otherwise relating to your breach of any representation or warranty hereunder and/or related to any 
                    claims arising from any negotiations or agreements with any lender.</li><br/>
                <!--</ol>-->
                
                    <h5>CANCELLATION POLICIES</h5>
                <!--<ol>-->
                    <li>This  Agreement can only be canceled after TBC receives written cancellation provided by me. Any such cancellation shall not 
                    relieve me from any payment or other obligations and responsibilities under paragraphs (9) and (10) above. From the date of written 
                    cancellation, TBC has the right to review and access any and all credit reports for verification purposes only. I agree and accept 
                    that I do not have the right to cancel this ninety-day (90-day) credit review process.</li><br/>
                
                    <h5>COMMERCIAL LOANS</h5>
                    
                    <li>TBC Services are also available for commercial loans. In the event that you desire TBC Services regarding a commercial loan, 
                    including but not limited to merchant cash advance or accounts receivables based loans, then all terms and conditions of this 
                    Agreement shall apply to any commercial loan, including but not limited to consents, authorizations, consulting fees, warranties 
                    and representations. In addition to any information required as specified above, you understand that in order to provide TBC 
                    Services in relation to a commercial loan it may be necessary for TBC to obtain consumer, personal, business and investigative 
                    reports and other information about you and/or your company (if the loan is to be made to an entity), including credit card 
                    processor statements and bank statements, from one or more consumer reporting agencies, such as TransUnion, Experian and 
                    Equifax, and from other credit bureaus, banks, creditors and other third parties. It may also be necessary to transmit the 
                    foregoing information to third parties in order to provide of TBC Services in connection with a commercial loan. You  also 
                    consent to the release by any creditor or financial institution of any of the foregoing information to TBC and/or its representatives 
                    , successors, assigns and designees.  You authorize TBC to obtain and/or transmit the foregoing information. You also warrant that you 
                    are authorized to act on behalf of and bind any entity for which you request that TBC Services be provided. You agree that you are 
                    individually responsible for payment of consulting fees regardless of whether the loan is funded to an entity.</li><br/>
                
                    <h5>MISCELLANEOUS</h5>
                    
                    <li>This Agreement contains the entire agreement of the Parties, and it may only be modified by an agreement in writing signed by 
                    all Parties. This Agreement shall be construed and interpreted in accordance with the substantive laws of the State of Florida, 
                    without regard to its conflict of laws principles. This Agreement is deemed entered into in the State of Florida and for any 
                    dispute arising out of or under this Agreement, or which are related to this Agreement, venue and jurisdiction shall be exclusively 
                    in Broward County, Florida and the Parties hereby consent to venue and jurisdiction in Broward County, Florida. In connection with 
                    any litigation arising out of or under this Agreement, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover all costs and reasonable 
                    attorney's fees including appellate and post judgment proceedings. I hereby authorize TBC to communicate with me via the e-mail 
                    address I have provided.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    I agree to the aforementioned terms and conditions making this a binding contract. I understand that this Agreement is bound by 
                    electronic signature.  This electronic signature must be that of the actual individual applying for a loan otherwise it constitutes 
                    forgery under any and all applicable state and federal laws, statutes, rules, and regulations. The individual "signing" this document 
                    affirms that the facts stated herein are true.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    I understand that I am giving consent to The Borrowing Club (TBC) permission to obtain a soft credit check to qualify me for obtaining 
                    a loan.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    I understand that by clicking on the I AGREE button or typing my name whichever is applicable immediately following this notice I am 
                    providing “written instructions” to TBC under the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA) authorizing TBC to obtain information from my 
                    personal credit profile or other information from any credit bureau, including but not limited to, Experian, TransUnion and/or 
                    Equifax. I authorize TBC to obtain such information solely to prequalify me for credit options.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    </li>
                
                </ol>
                <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>                
                <div class="row"><div class="col-12">
                    <span>IDENTITY VERIFICATION QUESTIONS:</span>
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-4">
                                        First Name :
                                    </div>
                                <div class="col-8">
                                    <span t-field="o.first_name"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-3">
                                        Last Name :
                                    </div>
                                <div class="col-9">
                                    <span t-field="o.last_name"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-2">Home Address :</div>
                        <div class="col-10">
                            <span t-field="o.street"/>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-4">Yearly Income :</div>
                                <div class="col-8">
                                    <span t-field="o.primary_gross_annual_income"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">Is The Income Verifiable? Yes_No :</div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span t-esc="o.is_income_verifiable"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <span>AGREE TO ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS:</span>
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-5">Signature :</div>
                                <div class="col-7"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-5">Date :</div>
                                <div class="col-7"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-6">AGREE TO ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS:</div>
                        <div class="col-6"/>
                    </div>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col-5">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-5">Signature :</div>
                                <div class="col-7"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-7">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-7">Date :</div>
                                <div class="col-5"/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    
                </div></div>
                <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                
                <div class="row text-left">
                    <h3><center>THIRD-PARTY AUTHORIZATION FORM</center></h3>
                </div>    
                    <p>
                        I,					with an address of						 (“Borrower” or “I” or “me” or “my”) hereby authorize 
                        THE BORROWING CLUB, LLC, its associates, agents and/or assigns (individually and collectively the “Agent”) the 
                        right to communicate with independent lenders (“Third-Parties”) on my behalf, and act as my agent, under the 
                        following terms:
                        <br/>
                        <ol>
                            <li> I hereby give and grant unto my said Agent full <b>consent and authority</b> to act for me in any lawful way 
                            with respect to the consent to obtain, share, release, discuss, and otherwise provide to Third Parties, and 
                            with each other, public and non-public personal information contained in or related to obtaining a consumer 
                            loan for the Borrower. This information may include but is not limited to the name, mailing address, 
                            telephone number, social security number, credit score, credit report, income, account balances, program 
                            eligibility, and payment activity of the Borrower.</li>
                            
                            <br/>
                            
                            <li>I understand that I will be fully responsible for reviewing any information that is sent by Third Parties 
                            to my Agent.</li>
                        
                            <br/>
                            
                            <li>This Authorization expires one year from the date signed unless Borrower specifically notified Agent in 
                            writing that this Authorization is of no further force and effect.</li>
                        
                            <br/>
                            
                            <li>I understand that this Form may not be accepted by some Third Parties, and my Agent will notify me in 
                            writing if it is not accepted.</li>
                            
                            <br/>
                        
                            <li>I understand and agree that my Agent has no responsibility or liability to verify what the Third 
                            Parties do with the information provided to it by my Agent, as authorized by this Form.</li>
                        
                            <br/>
                        
                            <li>I hereby agree to indemnify and forever hold my Agent harmless from any and all actions and causes 
                            of actions, suits, claims, attorney’s fees, or demands against my Agent, resulting from my Agent discussing, 
                            or declining to discuss, my information with Third-Parties, or resulting from my Agent providing, or 
                            declining to provide, any documents or other information to Third-Parties.</li>
                        </ol>
                        <br/>
                        <span> I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS THIRD-PARTY AUTHORIZATION.</span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>Borrower's Signature</span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>Borrower Printed Name: </span>
                        <span t-field="o.full_name"/>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>Date</span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                    </p>



                                            <!--For Maryland-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'MD' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h4><center><u>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</u></center></h4>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, at any time prior to midnight of 
                    the third business day after the date the contract is signed. If you cancel, any payment made by you 
                    under this contract will be returned within 10 days following receipt by the seller of your cancellation
                    notice. To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed and dated copy of this cancellation notice, or
                    any other written notice, to </p><br/>
                    
                    <p>The Borrowing Club, LLC. At 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069. <br/>
                        Not later than midnight ______________(Date).<br/>
                        I hereby cancel this transaction.</p><br/>
                        
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-5">(Date) :</div>
                                    <div class="col-7"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">(Customer Signature) :</div>
                                    <div class="col-5"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    
                    </t>
                    
                                            <!--For Oklohama-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'OK' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, at any time prior to midnight of the third 
                    business day after the date the contract is signed. If you cancel, any payment made by you under this 
                    contract will be returned within 10 days following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice. 
                    To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed and dated copy of this cancellation notice, or any 
                    other written notice, to The Borrowing Club, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202, Pompano Beach, FL 33069.</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>Not later than midnight				(Date) </p>
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction.</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">(Date)</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">(Customer Signature) :</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h4><center><u><b>INFORMATION STATEMENT</b></u></center></h4>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>The Borrowing Club, LLC </p>
                    
                    <p>555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202</p>
                    
                    <p>Pompano Beach, FL 33069</p>
                    
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>We are required by law to provide this information statement before the execution of a contract or 
                    before the receipt of any money or other valuable consideration.</p>
                    
                    <ol>
                        <li>You have the right to review any file maintained by any consumer credit reporting agency, as provided under 
                        the Federal Fair Credit Reporting Act, 15 U.S.C., Sections 1681 through 1681t.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>You have the right to review the above-mentioned file at no charge if a request is made to the 
                        consumer credit reporting agency within thirty (30) days after receiving notice that credit has been 
                        denied. If credit was not denied the approximate price to review such file will be $100.00.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>You have the right to dispute the completeness or accuracy of any item contained in your file 
                        which is maintained by a consumer credit reporting agency.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>In this paragraph give your customer a detailed description of the services to be performed 
                        by your company including the total amount the buyer will have to pay, or become obligated to pay,
                        for your services.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                        
                        <li>You have the right to proceed against the bond or trust account we are required by law to maintain.
                        The name and address of the surety company that issued the bond is International Fidelity Insurance 
                        Company.</li>
                        
                        <br/>
                    </ol>
                    
                    <p>I have received a copy of the above information statement.</p>
                    
                    
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>_______________________________</p>
                    
                    <p>Customer Signature</p>
                    
                    <p>_______________________________</p>
                    
                    <p>Date</p>
                    
                    
                    </t>
                    
                    
                                            <!--For Nebraska-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'NE' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days from the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract, will be returned with ten (10) days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice. To cancel this contract, mail or 
                    deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, or any other written notice to 
                    The Borrowing Club, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069 not later than
                    midnight on___________</p>
                    <br/>
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction,______________________(date).</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Signature :</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    </t>
                                                
                                                
                                                
                                            <!--For Pennsylvania-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'PA' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days from the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>If you cancel, any payment made by you under this contract will be returned within ten days 
                    after the date of receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice.</p>
                    
                    <p> To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, 
                    or any other written notice to:</p>
                    
                    <p><b>The Borrowing Club, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069</b> not later than
                    midnight (Date)___________</p>
                    
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction.</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Date :</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Purchaser's Signature :</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                            </div>
                        </div>  
                    </t>
                    
                    
                    
                                            <!--For Wisconsin-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'WI' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within five (5) days after the date on <b>which the contract is signed.</b> </p>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract will be returned within 15 days
                    following receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice.</p>
                    
                    <p> To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed and dated copy of this cancellation notice, 
                    or any other written notice to: The Borrowing Club, LLC at 555 SW 12th 
                    Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069 not later than midnight (Date)___________</p>
                    
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction.</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-8">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-6">Print Consumer Name</div>
                                    <div class="col-6">_________________________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <br/>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-6">Signature :</div>
                                    <div class="col-6">_________________________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <br/>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-6">Date :</div>
                                    <div class="col-6">_________________________________</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-4">
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        
                    </t>
                    
                                            <!--For West Virginia-->
                    <t t-if="o.state_id.code == 'WV' ">
                    <div style="page-break-before: always;"/>
                    <h5><center><u><b>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION</b></u></center></h5>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>You may cancel this contract, without any penalty or obligation, 
                    within three (3) days after the date the contract is signed.</p>
                    <br/>
                    
                    <p>If you cancel any payment made by you under this contract will be returned within ten (10) days
                    after the date of receipt by the seller of your cancellation notice.</p>
                    
                    <p> To cancel this contract, mail or deliver a signed dated copy of this cancellation notice, 
                    or any other written notice to:</p>
                    
                    <p><b>The Borrowing Club, LLC at 555 SW 12th Ave. Ste. 202 Pompano Beach, FL 33069</b> not later than
                    midnight (Date)___________</p>
                    
                    <p>I hereby cancel this transaction.</p>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Date :</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">______________________</div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-7">Purchaser's Signature :</div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-7">
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                    
                    


            </div>
                    
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
           </t>
       </t>
   </template>
</odoo>